It took a bunch of girls to make him man up.
The Winning Season is a comedy, drama film directed by Jim Strouse.
A comedy centered on a has-been coach who is given a shot at redemption when
he's asked to run his local high school's girls basketball team
Bill, played by Sam Rockwell.
Abby, played by Emma Roberts.
Terry, played by Rob Corddry.
Kathy, played by Emily Rios.
Wendy, played by Rooney Mara.
Stacey, played by Jessica Hecht.
The Winning Season is a 2009 American sports comedy
film written and directed by James C.
Strouse, and starring Sam Rockwell.
It premiered at the 2009 Sundance Film Festival and received a
limited theatrical release on September 3, 2010.
The film was distributed by Lionsgate in both the United States and the United
Kingdom, after the company acquired the rights at Sundance.
It was produced by Plum Pictures and Gigi Films.
The film explores themes of immigrant, sports, alcohol, bus ride, restaurant.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.